Folks, as many of you know, we're having trouble passing the budget this year.
Because the town's emergency reserve fund is only 10% of the budget,
Andover can't just delay sending out the tax bills or we risk running out of money.
The Board of Selectmen set a mill rate at a June 24 special meeting based on their best estimate of what the final town budget will be.
This allows the tax bills to go out on time.
They chose to set the mill rate at 36,
which is 0.39
mills higher than the current mill rate.
If the budget that is eventually approved is higher or lower than what the Board of Select and set, the town may need to send out a correction later.
Tax bills will be going out in the next few days.
The first installment is due on 07/01/2021.
Payments must be postmarked, paid online, or brought to the town hall by 08/02/2021
to avoid an interest charge.
Thank you for your patience during a difficult budget process.